BANUPRIYA KRISHNA...

SOFTWARE/DOCUMENTATION ASSISTANT



- Female
- 03/05/1993
- 07721405918
- banupriyacse0@gmail.com
- Peterlee, England

SKILLS

Language

English, Telugu, Tamil

Computer

Word, Excel, Power point

Computer

HTML5, CSS, Java Script

Computer

SAP

CERTIFICATIONS

2014: Sample certification's title

INTERESTS

I like net surfing, music, online games

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

banupriyacseO@gmail.com 07721405918,Peterlee England

banupriya 🗴

Four Years of Experience in handling SAP related activities and Creating, maintaining, reviewing Production departments documentation like SOP(Standard Operating Procedure), MBR (Manufacturing Batch Record), interested in using my extensive FULL STACK development skills at your organisation. I am interested in growing my skill set in an entry level position while contributing to your organisation's continued success.

EDUCATION

OBJECTIVE

P.S.R Rengasamy college of engineering for women's, Anna University

Computer science and engineering

May 2011 - June 2014

- - Front End

WORK EXPERIENCE

Bristol laboratories(pharmaceutical), England

Documentation reviewer /SAP activities

2022 - now

Data maintaining in SAP SYSTEM, Production Documents reviewing like MBR,SOP preparation and revising the MBR .preparation and updating staff's training records. In process checks for product(Tablets)etc.

Bristol laboratories(pharmaceutical), England

Documentation reviewer /SAP activities

2020 - 2021

Data maintaining in SAP SYSTEM, Production Documents reviewing like MBR,SOP preparation and revising the M and updating staff's training records. In process checks for p banu 🗴

UPMS

2015 - 2017 Teacher

ACTIVITIES

Entri Elevate

Full Stack Development 2023 - now

learning Full Stack Development course

RASI EDUCATION SYSTEM

System administrator/Teacher 2009 - 2011

Conducting the class about basic of computers.

© goodcv.com